<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:vcard="http://www.w3.org/2006/vcard/ns#"
         xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#"
         xmlns:nwda="https://github.com/ewg118/nwda-editor#"
         xmlns:arch="http://purl.org/archival/vocab/arch#"
         xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/"
         xmlns:foaf="http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/"
         xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#">
	<arch:Archive rdf:about="nwda:orsaw">
      <foaf:name>Willamette University Archives and Special Collections</foaf:name>
      <foaf:homepage rdf:resource="http://library.willamette.edu/archives/"/>
      <vcard:hasEmail rdf:resource="mailto:archives@willamette.edu"/>
      <vcard:hasAddress>
         <rdf:Description>
            <vcard:street-address>Archives and Special Collection</vcard:street-address>
            <vcard:street-address>Mark O. Hatfield Library</vcard:street-address>
            <vcard:street-address>900 State Street</vcard:street-address>
            <vcard:locality>Salem, OR</vcard:locality>
            <vcard:postal-code>97301</vcard:postal-code>
         </rdf:Description>
      </vcard:hasAddress>
      <vcard:hasTelephone>
         <vcard:Voice>
            <vcard:hasValue rdf:resource="tel:+5033706866"/>
         </vcard:Voice>
      </vcard:hasTelephone>
      <vcard:hasTelephone>
         <vcard:Fax>
            <vcard:hasValue rdf:resource="tel:+5033706141"/>
         </vcard:Fax>
      </vcard:hasTelephone>
      <nwda:visitation>Willamette University Archives and Special Collections is located on the 2nd floor of the Mark O. Hatfield Library and is open 9:00 - noon; 1:00 - 4:00 Monday - Friday, with the exception of Willamette University holidays. The Archives and Special Collections welcomes users from the Willamette community as well as members of the public.</nwda:visitation>
      <nwda:facsimile>A list of reproduction services offered by the Archives and Special Collections is available here: http://library.willamette.edu/archives/policies/repro/ For permission to publish, quote, broadcast, perform, or exhibit, contact the University Archivist at: http://library.willamette.edu/archives/contact/</nwda:facsimile>
      <dcterms:description>Archives and Special Collections collects, preserves, and makes available University records of enduring value and primary source materials focusing on the Northwest. This rich collection is a valuable resource for researchers, historians and the general public. Of particular note are Congressional and political papers and the Pacific Northwest Artists Archive. Special Collections include such treasures as a 15th century book of hours, a second folio edition of Shakespeare's plays, and a first edition of Samuel Johnson's dictionary.</dcterms:description>
   </arch:Archive>
</rdf:RDF>